<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>qiskit on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/tags/qiskit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in qiskit on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/tags/qiskit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Programming API</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-programming-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-programming-api/</guid>
      <description>About The goal of this project is to provide a quantum programming API that will help people who want to incorporate quantum speed-ups into their classical programs much easier.
This project aims to both create the infrastructure to communicate with quantum systems and to create with that same infrastructure. We hope that our efforts in building this can lead to inspiration and further advances with the use of quantum computing in the broader computer science community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit/</guid>
      <description>Qiskit is IBM&amp;rsquo;s open source quantum computing SDK. There is a vibrant community of open source developers and quantum advocates.
Getting Started Join the Qiskit slack!
Here are some curated tutorials to get yourself started with Qiskit and the IBM Quantum Experience:
Code your first quantum circuit CH 1-3 of Qiskit Textbook Beginner Tutorials Events Stay up to date with Qiskit events.
Past events:
Hackathons IBM Qiskit Global Summer School Quantum Advocates Apply to become one of ~200 Quantum Advocate across ~30 countries at IBM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>qtcodes</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qtcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qtcodes/</guid>
      <description>Status qtcodes is published on PyPI with tooling to encode, decode and benchmark XXXX/ZZZZ surface code, XZZX surface code, and repetition code!
About We are building Encoder and Minimum Weight Perfect Matching Graph Decoder tools for serveral Topological Codes we wish to implement in Qiskit Ignis.
Here is the Github repo: https://github.com/yaleqc/qtcodes
Here is a link to our project proposal.
Team The first iteration of this project was created by members Shantanu Jha &amp;lsquo;21, Henry Liu &amp;lsquo;21, Will Sun &amp;lsquo;22, Shraddha Singh (Grad), and Andy Ding (Grad).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
