<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resources on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/categories/resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resources on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/categories/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Opportunities Bulletin</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/opportunities-bulletin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/opportunities-bulletin/</guid>
      <description>Here is a collection of opportunities spanning research projects, internships, hackathons, and more! This list is updated weekly.
Week of Apr 18, 2021   IBM Quantum Community Partnerships Intern role
 Join IBM Quantum and help their team strengthen the quantum community from the first introduction to quantum through to quantum computing research and development. IBM Quantum Community Partnership Interns will have the opportunity to work on projects related to blogging, scientific and technical writing, quantum education, outreach, community events, and open-source software, among other areas of focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YuQC Resources and Knowledge Database</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/yuqc-resources-and-knowledge-database/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/yuqc-resources-and-knowledge-database/</guid>
      <description>Please take a look through the following database for resources that will help you learn more about quantum computation and quantum information science. Use the organizational features to sort items by type or by difficult level to suit your specific needs, or search directly for items!
YuQC Resource Database
To suggest other items to add to our database, please reach out to the Director of Resources: Shoumik Chowdhury. Additionally, PDFs of certain texts may be available upon request &amp;mdash; reach out to learn more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Please take a moment to explore our site and read this post from our Fall 2020 interest meeting to learn a bit more about our organization. Then, please read through the following onboarding guide for new YuQC members.
Sign-Up Please fill out this membership interest form (https://forms.gle/X2k8scLqNkgsvLv1A) to join the Yale Undergrad Quantum Computing group mailing list, Discord and more. Most of our discussion is held over Discord.
Join a Project Learn how to join existing projects and even propose new projects here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Information Science classes at Yale</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-information-science-classes-at-yale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-information-science-classes-at-yale/</guid>
      <description>Here is a growing list of Yale classes with applications towards Quantum Information Science. Much more coming soon.
Quantum Information  Physics 345: Introduction to Quantum Information Processing and Communication, Prof Steven Girvin  Who should take it: Anyone with a knowledge of complex numbers and introductory linear algebra. This course presents a very accessible and exciting foray into quantum information science. This is highly recommended to anyone looking to begin their journey with quantum computing, with or without a technical physics background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Quantum Institute</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/yale-quantum-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/yale-quantum-institute/</guid>
      <description>Here is a growing list of interdisciplinary Yale efforts in Quantum Computing under the umbrella of the Yale Quantum Institute.
Useful Sites  quantuminstitute.yale.edu  Yale Quantum Institute Events Institute History Institute Members Join the mailing list!   quantum.yale.edu  A collection of quantum computing research efforts and labs at Yale looking into topics spanning Physics, Applied Physics, Chemistry, Computer Science, and Engineering. Information about the Quantum Week at Yale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open-source Resources</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/open-source-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/open-source-resources/</guid>
      <description>Here are some resources to help you along with your open source quantum endeavours.
QC Open Source Projects
Quantum Open Source Foundation
 Open Source Projects Mentorship Learning Prizes and Funding Projects  Unitary Fund
 Non-profit Microgrants Research projects  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit/</guid>
      <description>Qiskit is IBM&amp;rsquo;s open source quantum computing SDK. There is a vibrant community of open source developers and quantum advocates.
Getting Started Join the Qiskit slack!
Here are some curated tutorials to get yourself started with Qiskit and the IBM Quantum Experience:
 Code your first quantum circuit CH 1-3 of Qiskit Textbook Beginner Tutorials  Events Stay up to date with Qiskit events.
Past events:
 Hackathons IBM Qiskit Global Summer School  Quantum Advocates Apply to become one of ~200 Quantum Advocate across ~30 countries at IBM.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
