<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>foundations on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/tags/foundations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in foundations on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/tags/foundations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Please take a moment to explore our site and read this post from our Fall 2020 interest meeting to learn a bit more about our organization. Then, please read through the following onboarding guide for new YuQC members.
Sign-Up Please fill out this membership interest form (https://forms.gle/X2k8scLqNkgsvLv1A) to join the Yale Undergrad Quantum Computing group mailing list, Discord and more. Most of our discussion is held over Discord.
Join a Project Learn how to join existing projects and even propose new projects here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Classes towards Quantum Information Science</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/yale-classes-towards-quantum-information-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/yale-classes-towards-quantum-information-science/</guid>
      <description>Here is a growing list of Yale classes with applications towards Quantum Information Science. Much more coming soon.
Quantum Information  Physics 345: Introduction to Quantum Information Processing and Communication, Prof Steven Girvin  Who should take it: Anyone with a knowledge of complex numbers and introductory linear algebra. This course presents a very accessible and exciting foray into quantum information science. This is highly recommended to anyone looking to begin their journey with quantum computing, with or without a technical physics background.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
