<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/categories/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/categories/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare for the Quantum Workforce Series</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/how-to-prepare-for-the-quantum-workforce-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/how-to-prepare-for-the-quantum-workforce-series/</guid>
      <description>Information Our advisor Florian Carle is hosting a cool professional development panel about working in quantum startups on Oct 29 at 4 pm! See details below.
More information: https://quantuminstitute.yale.edu/resources/how-join-quantum-workforce
Link to register: https://yale.zoom.us/webinar/register/WN_iW2BwsRWS4KSZ4C3ugVO-w
Other events that might be interesting!
Public Talk - Sean Carroll: The Many Worlds of Quantum Mechanics - Tuesday, November 2, 2021 - 5:00pm https://quantuminstitute.yale.edu/event/public-talk-sean-carroll-many-worlds-quantum-mechanics
How to Join the Quantum Workforce? – Prepare for Industry - Friday, December 10, 2021 - 4:00pm https://quantuminstitute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Series (Spring 2021)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/speaker-series-spring-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/speaker-series-spring-2021/</guid>
      <description>Here is a summary and schedule of the YuQC Speaker Series.
 Information &amp;amp; Recordings Check out this Youtube playlist of all past talk recordings!!
Please click here (yale.edu account required) to access zoom links, meeting passwords, and, eventually, recordings for this speaker series.
 Dr. Zlatko Minev To catch and reverse a quantum jump mid-flight April 21, 7:00PM-8:00PM ET Dr. Minev is a scientist with an applied experimental and theoretical background, focused on quantum computing and fundamental physics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Coalition Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-coalition-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-coalition-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Attend Please visit quantumcoalition.io to learn more about this exciting virtual hackathon co-hosted by Yale and Stanford, open to everyone, and sponsored by Quantum Computing industry innovators.
Registration launches on February 14, 2021!
Join the Organizing Committee If you are a YuQC member interested in joining the QC Hack Organizing Committee, please sign up here.
Sponsors Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2020 Interest Meeting</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/fall-2020-interest-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/fall-2020-interest-meeting/</guid>
      <description>The Fall 2020 interest meeting was held on Nov 22nd, 2020 from 1:00PM to 1:30PM ET.
Thanks so much to everyone who could make it.
If you were unable to attend the event, absolutely no worries. Please take a moment to view (yale.edu email required) the recording and the slides from the meeting.
Summary  Over 60+ form submissions, with 30+ interest meeting attendees! Each member is involved with at least one &amp;ldquo;project&amp;rdquo;: open-source project, tutorials, hackathon planning outreach, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
