<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shantanu Jha (President 2020-21, Founder)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/shantanu-jha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/shantanu-jha/</guid>
      <description>President (2020-21) Physics and Mathematics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github, Email Shantanu ’21 is a Math and Physics major and a member of Saybrook College. He founded YuQC to provide a support network to help younger or otherwise newcomer students explore the often daunting but wonderfully interdisciplinary field of quantum information science. His research spans quantum information theory work with Steven Girvin, terahertz wireless communications (6G) with Federico Capasso, and most recently, experimental quantum computation with Michel Devoret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andy Ding (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/andy-ding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/andy-ding/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Ph.D. Student LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayelet Kalfus (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/ayelet-kalfus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/ayelet-kalfus/</guid>
      <description>Director of Partnerships (2020-21) Physics with Computer Science certificate, Class of 2024 (Gap Year) LinkedIn, Github Ayelet Kalfus is a rising sophomore majoring in physics, with a certificate in computer science. Intrigued by quantum computers’ potential to transform our lives, Ayelet is super excited to join YuQC, learning with and from the entire group. Outside of physics, Ayelet loves reading, writing, film, and exploring new cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/jean-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/jean-wang/</guid>
      <description>Director of Invited Talks (2020-21) Math and Humanities, Class of 2024 Github Jean is a first-year in Jonathan Edwards College planning to double major in Mathematics and Humanities. She is interested in the mathematics of quantum cryptography and optimizing quantum algorithms. Outside of quantum, she enjoys writing stories and listening to radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessie Chen (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/jessie-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/jessie-chen/</guid>
      <description>Treasurer Physics and Computer Science, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikhil Harle (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/nikhil-harle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/nikhil-harle/</guid>
      <description>Director of Events Physics, Class of 2023 Github Nikhil is a rising junior and intensive physics major and was previously a fellow at the Center for Quantum Devices in Copenhagen. His interests include preserving quantum information through novel methods of error correction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sami Alves (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/sami-alves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/sami-alves/</guid>
      <description>Social Chair Physics and Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seun Omonije (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/seun-omonije/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/seun-omonije/</guid>
      <description>Director of Open Source Projects (2020-21) Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn | Github Bio: Oluseun (Seun) Omonije &amp;lsquo;22 is a Computer Science major from Dallas, TX in Silliman College. A two-time Google Intern, Seun got started in quantum during the summer of 2020 while attending a Google AI Quantum event. Since then, he spent a semester as a research assistant for Prof. Lin Zhong&amp;rsquo;s Efficient Computing Lab, helping to solve problems pertaining to quantum error correction, specifically optimizations to the control system between QEC decoders and physical quantum system, as well as the algorithms running within these control systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoumik Chowdhury (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</guid>
      <description>Director of Resources (2020-21) Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github As a long-time enthusiast of quantum computing, I am incredibly excited that a club like YuQC now exists at Yale. I am really looking forward to meeting other people interested in quantum science, and getting to learn from them — as well as being able to share what I have learned during my years working in this area. Given that Yale is a world-leading institution for quantum information science, it is only fitting that we have a proper undergraduate club dedicated to this field — I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what this group gets up to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opportunities Bulletin</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/opportunities-bulletin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/opportunities-bulletin/</guid>
      <description>Here is a collection of opportunities spanning research projects, internships, hackathons, and more! This list is updated weekly.
Week of Mar 7, 2021   Women in Quantum Summit IV
 Register to attend the fourth Women in Quantum virtual summit. The event will feature more than a dozen noted speakers and panelists, and will offer a unique career fair to pair employers in the emerging quantum industry with women desiring or progressing in careers in quantum computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argyrios Giannisis Manes (Project Leader 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/argyrios-giannisis-manes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/argyrios-giannisis-manes/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn, Github Argyris Giannisis Manes is a first-year in Trumbull College, was born in Athens and now lives in Volos, Greece. He intends to major in Mathematics and Physics, and his interests include Math, Physics, CS, Astronomy, Music, Debate, Juggling, and more! He’s been interested in Quantum Computing for a long time, and is really excited to finally have the opportunity to explore Quantum Information alongside peers and mentors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Foxman (Project Leader 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/ben-foxman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/ben-foxman/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Computer Science, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github I&amp;rsquo;m a sophomore in Pauli Murray College, double majoring in computer science and math. Quantum Computation interests me because of how many applications would be unlocked when the physical limitations of classical computers. I&amp;rsquo;m especially curious about the vast improvements that could be made to artificial intelligence, and what would be possible for Quantum Computers to &amp;ldquo;learn&amp;rdquo; in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben McDonough (Project Leader 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/ben-mcdonough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/ben-mcdonough/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2024 Github Ben loves physics and wants to find a way to join his passions for mathematics, computer science, and theoretical physics. His favorite aspect of Yale is the emphasis on peer support and community bonds, which he feels the interdisciplinary study of quantum information and quantum computing strongly exemplifies. He loves the &amp;lsquo;spooky action at a distance&amp;rsquo; counter-intuitive weirdness of the quantum world, and is excited to be studying physics at Yale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yiğit Kılıçoğlu (Project Leader 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/yigit-kilicoglu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/yigit-kilicoglu/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Physics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn Yiğit is interested in the mathematics of quantum computation. Having a background in programming, he is also into quantum cryptography. Outside of academics, Yiğit is an avid tennis, piano and accordion player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Householder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/aaron-householder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/aaron-householder/</guid>
      <description>Astrophysics, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barkotel Fesseha Zemenu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/barkotel-zemenu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/barkotel-zemenu/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2024 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deyuan Li</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/deyuan-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/deyuan-li/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Mathematics, Class of 2024 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francis Fedora</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/francis-fedora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/francis-fedora/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2023 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aidan Evans</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/aidan-evans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/aidan-evans/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Philosophy, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github Aidan Evans is a sophomore double majoring and computer science and philosophy. He has completed courses in advanced algorithm design and theory of computation for traditional computers along with extensive programming experience in multiple languages. He hopes to learn more about quantum computation and gain experience designing and programming quantum algorithms. In general, Aidan enjoys to challenge himself and apply what he has learned in practical and meaningful ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allen Mi</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/allen-mi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/allen-mi/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Computer Science, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amanda Butler</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/amanda-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/amanda-butler/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Astronomy, Class of 2022 Amanda (JE &amp;lsquo;22) is a double major in Physics &amp;amp; Astronomy, broadly interested in experimental techniques and cosmology. She is eager to explore Quantum Computing &amp;amp; Information Science since she has had less exposure to it in her primary fields, but is excited for the ways in which QC will likely revolutionize all scientific disciplines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Yee</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/brandon-yee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/brandon-yee/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2024 Github I got pulled over for speeding once. The officer asked me if I knew how fast I was going. I said &amp;ldquo;no, but I know where I am.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry Liu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/henry-liu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/henry-liu/</guid>
      <description>Applied Physics, Class of 2021 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang Huaijin</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/jean-wang-huaijin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/jean-wang-huaijin/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Philosophy, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Blanco</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/jorge-blanco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/jorge-blanco/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Statistics and Data Science, Class of 2023-4 (Gap Semester) LinkedIn, Github Jorge Blanco is a sophomore studying Mathematics and Statistics and Data Science. His academic interests are quantitative finance and mathematical statistics. He is interested in learning about quantum computation because its applications have world-changing potential. Specifically, he is interested in exploring the ways quantum computation, through the use of quantum optimization algorithms, can be applied to solve problems in finance and other fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katerina Kargioti</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/katerina-kargioti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/katerina-kargioti/</guid>
      <description>Applied Physics, Class of 2023 Github Hi! My name is Katerina and I am a sophomore in Pauli Murray College. I am majoring in Applied Physis. I am interested in learning more about quantum computation due its potential to open new pathways for physics and science in general. It is also exciting to be part of a fast-growing field that is constantly developing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke Bell</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/luke-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/luke-bell/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics, Class of 2023 LinkedIn Luke Bell is a sophomore in Pierson College and a current mathematics major. On campus, he is involved in the Yale Federalist Party, Yale Undergraduate Piano Collective, Rural Students Alliance at Yale, the Yale Logos Magazine, and Christian Union Lux. Due to his interest in quantum mechanics, he desires to explore the computational power, potential, and novelty of quantum computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Tu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/matt-tu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/matt-tu/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github Through my CS major, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot about the inner workings about bit-centered traditional computing, including its physical limitations. I&amp;rsquo;m really interested in potentially being one of the first people to &amp;ldquo;write code&amp;rdquo; for that runs on a quantum computer. I feel like my background in lower-level systems programming can be a huge asset for the organization, and as a non-Physics major I can learn a lot about quantum mechanics in general!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sofia Fausone</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/sofia-fausone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/sofia-fausone/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Mathematics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn, Github Sofia is interested in learning more about quantum mechanics and quantum computing in particular. In high school, she participated in a summer research program about quantum mechanics and nanotechnology, focusing on coding and STMs. She is excited to explore quantum computation, especially since it is a fairly new field with enormous potential for physics and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yofti Milkessa</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/yofti-milkessa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/yofti-milkessa/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn I’m a CS major who has also dabbled in physics. I was curious about the idea of quantum computing so after a friend’s recommendation, I read Nielsen and Chuang’s book on quantum computation during the summer. I have since been even more fascinated about this field and I want to keep exploring it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yu Jun Shen</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/yu-jun-shen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/yu-jun-shen/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github Quantum computing is a rapidly developing field and can help us solve big problems in the near future. I want to learn more about this and Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing group is a great way to further my interest. I hope to meet fellow Yalies who are excited about this and explore some spooky physics soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Zhou</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/laura-zhou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/laura-zhou/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ines Chung-Halpern</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/ines-chung-halpern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/ines-chung-halpern/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malcolm Keyes</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/malcolm-keyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/malcolm-keyes/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suba Ramesh</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/suba-ramesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/suba-ramesh/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Class of 2024 LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Doyle</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/will-doyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/will-doyle/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github Will took physics 260-261 with Professor Girvin and thought that quantum computing sounds really interesting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Series (Spring 2021)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/speaker-series-spring-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/speaker-series-spring-2021/</guid>
      <description>Here is a summary and schedule of the YuQC Speaker Series.
 Information &amp;amp; Recordings Check out this Youtube playlist of all past talk recordings!!
Please click here (yale.edu account required) to access zoom links, meeting passwords, and, eventually, recordings for this speaker series.
 Prof. Michel Devoret Error correction of logical quantum bits March 26, Time TBA Currently the F. W. Beinecke Professor of Applied Physics at Yale University (which he joined in 2002), Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Cryptography</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-cryptography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-cryptography/</guid>
      <description>Status  About We are going through an edX course titled &amp;ldquo;Quantum Cryptography&amp;rdquo; to gain knowledge and experience in the field. Once a sufficient amount of fundamental concepts is learned, we will start to implement quantum network protocols for the Quantum Protocol Zoo, an open repository founded by our very own Shraddha Singh.
Project Lead: Yiğit Kılıçoğlu, Argyris Giannisis Manes
Team: Sami Alves, Ines Chung-Halpern, Sofia Fausone, Francis Fedora, Allen Mi Ryan Bose-Roy, Will Sun, Barkotel Zemenu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YuQC Resources and Knowledge Database</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/yuqc-resources-and-knowledge-database/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/yuqc-resources-and-knowledge-database/</guid>
      <description>Please take a look through the following database for resources that will help you learn more about quantum computation and quantum information science. Use the organizational features to sort items by type or by difficult level to suit your specific needs, or search directly for items!
YuQC Resource Database
To suggest other items to add to our database, please reach out to the Director of Resources: Shoumik Chowdhury. Additionally, PDFs of certain texts may be available upon request &amp;mdash; reach out to learn more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Programming API</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-programming-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-programming-api/</guid>
      <description>About The goal of this project is to provide a quantum programming API that will help people who want to incorporate quantum speed-ups into their classical programs much easier.
This project aims to both create the infrastructure to communicate with quantum systems and to create with that same infrastructure. We hope that our efforts in building this can lead to inspiration and further advances with the use of quantum computing in the broader computer science community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulation and Optimization of Quantum Error Correction Circuits</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/simulation-and-optimization-of-quantum-error-correction-circuits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/simulation-and-optimization-of-quantum-error-correction-circuits/</guid>
      <description>About We are exploring quantum error correction and investigating tools for simulating quantum control systems. A full introduction and background on this project can be found on our project proposal.
Team This project was originally proposed by faculty sponsor Dr. Steven Girvin and is lead by member Ben McDonough.
Current contributing members include:
 Sofia Fausone Katrina Kargioti Allen Mi  Special thanks to senior member Jean Wang for providing additional academic support and guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Coalition Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-coalition-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-coalition-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Attend Please visit qchack.io to learn more about this exciting virtual hackathon co-hosted by Yale and Stanford, open to everyone, and sponsored by Quantum Computing industry innovators.
Registration launches on February 14, 2021!
Join the Organizing Committee If you are a YuQC member interested in joining the QC Hack Organizing Committee, please sign up here.
Sponsors Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Please take a moment to explore our site and read this post from our Fall 2020 interest meeting to learn a bit more about our organization. Then, please read through the following onboarding guide for new YuQC members.
Sign-Up Please fill out this membership interest form (https://forms.gle/X2k8scLqNkgsvLv1A) to join the Yale Undergrad Quantum Computing group mailing list, Discord and more. Most of our discussion is held over Discord.
Join a Project Learn how to join existing projects and even propose new projects here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Ideas</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/project-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/project-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Projects: efforts ranging open-source packages to hackathon events to resource development and more!
SUBMIT YOUR PROJECT IDEAS: Have an idea for a project? Click here to propose a project!
NOTE: Each project requires a corresponding project proposal that can be filled out and submitted later. Click here for the template for the write-up.
Join a project team: Want to see what we&amp;rsquo;re working on? Click here to check out our project spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2020 Interest Meeting</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/fall-2020-interest-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/fall-2020-interest-meeting/</guid>
      <description>The Fall 2020 interest meeting was held on Nov 22nd, 2020 from 1:00PM to 1:30PM ET.
Thanks so much to everyone who could make it.
If you were unable to attend the event, absolutely no worries. Please take a moment to view (yale.edu email required) the recording and the slides from the meeting.
Summary  Over 60+ form submissions, with 30+ interest meeting attendees! Each member is involved with at least one &amp;ldquo;project&amp;rdquo;: open-source project, tutorials, hackathon planning outreach, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Information Science classes at Yale</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-information-science-classes-at-yale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-information-science-classes-at-yale/</guid>
      <description>Here is a growing list of Yale classes with applications towards Quantum Information Science. Much more coming soon.
Quantum Information  Physics 345: Introduction to Quantum Information Processing and Communication, Prof Steven Girvin  Who should take it: Anyone with a knowledge of complex numbers and introductory linear algebra. This course presents a very accessible and exciting foray into quantum information science. This is highly recommended to anyone looking to begin their journey with quantum computing, with or without a technical physics background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Quantum Institute</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/yale-quantum-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/yale-quantum-institute/</guid>
      <description>Here is a growing list of interdisciplinary Yale efforts in Quantum Computing under the umbrella of the Yale Quantum Institute.
Useful Sites  quantuminstitute.yale.edu  Yale Quantum Institute Events Institute History Institute Members Join the mailing list!   quantum.yale.edu  A collection of quantum computing research efforts and labs at Yale looking into topics spanning Physics, Applied Physics, Chemistry, Computer Science, and Engineering. Information about the Quantum Week at Yale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open-source Resources</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/open-source-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/open-source-resources/</guid>
      <description>Here are some resources to help you along with your open source quantum endeavours.
QC Open Source Projects
Quantum Open Source Foundation
 Open Source Projects Mentorship Learning Prizes and Funding Projects  Unitary Fund
 Non-profit Microgrants Research projects  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit/</guid>
      <description>Qiskit is IBM&amp;rsquo;s open source quantum computing SDK. There is a vibrant community of open source developers and quantum advocates.
Getting Started Join the Qiskit slack!
Here are some curated tutorials to get yourself started with Qiskit and the IBM Quantum Experience:
 Code your first quantum circuit CH 1-3 of Qiskit Textbook Beginner Tutorials  Events Stay up to date with Qiskit events.
Past events:
 Hackathons IBM Qiskit Global Summer School  Quantum Advocates Apply to become one of ~200 Quantum Advocate across ~30 countries at IBM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit Surface Code Encoder and MWPM Decoder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</guid>
      <description>Status This open-source package was presented at the November 2020 Qiskit Advocate Demo Session and is pending official incorporating into Qiskit Ignis. Our immediate goal is to demonstrate the rotated surface code threshold point in simulation.
 About We are building a Surface Code Encoder and Minimum Weight Perfect Matching Decoder package for Qiskit Ignis.
Here is the Github repo: https://github.com/Phionx/qiskit_surface_codes
Here is a link to our project proposal.
Team The first iteration of this project was created by members Shantanu Jha &amp;lsquo;21, Henry Liu &amp;lsquo;21 and Will Sun &amp;lsquo;22 for IBM Qiskit Ignis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qubit by Qubit Initiative</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qubit-by-qubit-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qubit-by-qubit-initiative/</guid>
      <description>Apply for paid and volunteer opportunities at the Qubit by Qubit Initiative.
Here are some of their current projects:
 Developing homework, problem sets, or worksheets Developing middle or high school curricula for quantum Developing or editing content for textbook for high school students Developing quantum workshop for K-12 students Being a Teaching Assistant for intro course Teaching quantum workshops to K-12 students  Please reach out to member Shoumik Chowdhury &amp;lsquo;21 to learn more!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
