<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andy Ding (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/andy-ding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/andy-ding/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Ph.D. Student LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayelet Kalfus (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ayelet-kalfus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ayelet-kalfus/</guid>
      <description>Director of Partnerships (2020-21) Physics with Computer Science certificate, Class of 2024 (Gap Year) LinkedIn Ayelet Kalfus is a rising sophomore majoring in physics, with a certificate in computer science. Intrigued by quantum computers’ potential to transform our lives, Ayelet is super excited to join YuQC, learning with and from the entire group. Outside of physics, Ayelet loves reading, writing, film, and exploring new cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang/</guid>
      <description>Director of Invited Talks (2020-21) Math and Humanities, Class of 2024 Github Jean is a first-year in Jonathan Edwards College planning to double major in Mathematics and Humanities. She is interested in the mathematics of quantum cryptography and optimizing quantum algorithms. Outside of quantum, she enjoys writing stories and listening to radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikhil Harle (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/nikhil-harle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/nikhil-harle/</guid>
      <description>Director of Events Physics, Class of 2023 Github Nikhil is a rising junior and intensive physics major and was previously a fellow at the Center for Quantum Devices in Copenhagen. His interests include preserving quantum information through novel methods of error correction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seun Omonije (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/seun-omonije/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/seun-omonije/</guid>
      <description>Director of Open Source Projects (2020-21) Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn | Github Bio: Oluseun (Seun) Omonije &amp;lsquo;22 is a Computer Science major from Dallas, TX in Silliman College. A two-time Google Intern, Seun got started in quantum during the summer of 2020 while attending a Google AI Quantum event. Since then, he spent a semester as a research assistant for Prof. Lin Zhong&amp;rsquo;s Efficient Computing Lab, helping to solve problems pertaining to quantum error correction, specifically optimizations to the control system between QEC decoders and physical quantum system, as well as the algorithms running within these control systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shantanu Jha (President 2020-21, Founder)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shantanu-jha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shantanu-jha/</guid>
      <description>President (2020-21) Physics and Mathematics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github, Email Shantanu ’21 is a Math and Physics major and a member of Saybrook College. He founded YuQC to provide a support network to help younger or otherwise newcomer students explore the often daunting but wonderfully interdisciplinary field of quantum information science. His research spans quantum information theory work with Steven Girvin, terahertz wireless communications (6G) with Federico Capasso, and most recently, experimental quantum computation with Michel Devoret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoumik Chowdhury (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</guid>
      <description>Director of Resources (2020-21) Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github As a long-time enthusiast of quantum computing, I am incredibly excited that a club like YuQC now exists at Yale. I am really looking forward to meeting other people interested in quantum science, and getting to learn from them — as well as being able to share what I have learned during my years working in this area. Given that Yale is a world-leading institution for quantum information science, it is only fitting that we have a proper undergraduate club dedicated to this field — I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what this group gets up to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opportunities Bulletin</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/opportunities-bulletin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/opportunities-bulletin/</guid>
      <description>Here is a collection of opportunities spanning research projects, internships, hackathons, and more! This list is updated weekly.
Week of Jan 10, 2021  QHack:  QHack is a virtual hackathon hosted from Feb 17 to Feb 26th by Pennylane, a quantum machine learning company. Sign up here.    Week of Jan 3, 2021  PHYS 345: Introduction to Quantum Information Processing and Communication  Enroll in an excellent intro to QC taught by Prof Girvin in the Spring of 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Series (Spring 2021)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/speaker-series-spring-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/speaker-series-spring-2021/</guid>
      <description>Here is a summary and schedule of the YuQC Speaker Series.
 Prof. Steven Girvin, Yale The Second Quantum Revolution and the Race to Build ‘Impossible’ Computers February 9th, 7PM ET Professor Steven Girvin is a Eugene Higgins Professor of Physics at Yale, and the Director of the Co-Design Center for Quantum Advantage at Brookhaven National Laboratory.
Abstract: The first quantum revolution brought us the great technological advances of the 20th century—the transistor, the laser, the atomic clock and GPS, the global positioning system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Please take a moment to explore our site and read this post from our Fall 2020 interest meeting to learn a bit more about our organization. Then, please read through the following onboarding guide for new YuQC members.
Sign-Up Please fill out this membership interest form (https://forms.gle/X2k8scLqNkgsvLv1A) to join the Yale Undergrad Quantum Computing group mailing list, Discord and more. Most of our discussion is held over Discord.
Join a Project Learn how to join existing projects and even propose new projects here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Ideas</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/project-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/project-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Projects: efforts ranging open-source packages to hackathon events to resource development and more!
SUBMIT YOUR PROJECT IDEAS: Have an idea for a project? Click here to propose a project!
NOTE: Each project requires a corresponding project proposal that can be filled out and submitted later. Click here for the template for the write-up.
Get involved with a current project: Want to see what we&amp;rsquo;re working on? Click here to check out our project spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Householder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/aaron-householder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/aaron-householder/</guid>
      <description>Astrophysics, Class of 2023 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aidan Evans</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/aidan-evans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/aidan-evans/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Philosophy, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allen Mi</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/allen-mi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/allen-mi/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Computer Science, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Foxman</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ben-foxman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ben-foxman/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Computer Science, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github I&amp;rsquo;m a sophomore in Pauli Murray College, double majoring in computer science and math. Quantum Computation interests me because of how many applications would be unlocked when the physical limitations of classical computers. I&amp;rsquo;m especially curious about the vast improvements that could be made to artificial intelligence, and what would be possible for Quantum Computers to &amp;ldquo;learn&amp;rdquo; in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Yee</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/brandon-yee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/brandon-yee/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2024 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam Greene</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/cam-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/cam-greene/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Philosophy, Class of 2024 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connor Totilas</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/connor-totilas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/connor-totilas/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2024 I remember learning in 9th grade what a qubit was and I though it was the coolest thing ever. I find quantum mechanics to be absolutely fascinating and to me quantum information science is the pinnacle of our ability to harness quantum mechanics. I soon began teaching myself all about quantum computers until I was able to write a research paper about the fundamental properties of quantum computers my senior year in high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Qenani</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/daniel-qenani/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/daniel-qenani/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 LinkedIn I would like to be a part of this club in whatever capacity is most useful for the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall 2020 Interest Meeting</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/fall-2020-interest-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/fall-2020-interest-meeting/</guid>
      <description>The Fall 2020 interest meeting was held on Nov 22nd, 2020 from 1:00PM to 1:30PM ET.
Thanks so much to everyone who could make it.
If you were unable to attend the event, absolutely no worries. Please take a moment to view (yale.edu email required) the recording and the slides from the meeting.
Summary  Over 60+ form submissions, with 30+ interest meeting attendees! Each member is involved with at least one &amp;ldquo;project&amp;rdquo;: open-source project, tutorials, hackathon planning outreach, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanbai Lyu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/hanbai-lyu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/hanbai-lyu/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Mathematics, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hao Chen</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/hao-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/hao-chen/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Visiting Student 2019-2020 LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry Liu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/henry-liu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/henry-liu/</guid>
      <description>Applied Physics, Class of 2021 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang-huaijin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang-huaijin/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Philosophy, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessie Chen</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jessie-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jessie-chen/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Computer Science, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel Binu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/joel-binu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/joel-binu/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Blanco</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jorge-blanco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jorge-blanco/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and either Statistics and Data Science or Computer Science, Class of 2023-4 (Gap Semester) LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katerina Kargioti</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/katerina-kargioti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/katerina-kargioti/</guid>
      <description>Applied Physics, Class of 2023 Hi! My name is Katerina and I am a sophomore in Pauli Murray College. I am majoring in Applied Physis. I am interested in learning more about quantum computation due its potential to open new pathways for physics and science in general. It is also exciting to be part of a fast-growing field that is constantly developing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keon Azar</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/keon-azar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/keon-azar/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Economics, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kohsuke Sato</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/kohsuke-sato/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/kohsuke-sato/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github I am a junior majoring in Physics (Int.), and quantum computing is an area that I would like to pursue after graduation. This club interested me because I thought that this would be a great opportunity for myself to learn more about quantum computing and to get to know other students interested in it at Yale!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lenny Khazan</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/lenny-khazan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/lenny-khazan/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2021 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke Bell</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/luke-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/luke-bell/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics, Class of 2023 LinkedIn Luke Bell is a sophomore in Pierson College and a current mathematics major. On campus, he is involved in the Yale Federalist Party, Yale Undergraduate Piano Collective, Rural Students Alliance at Yale, the Yale Logos Magazine, and Christian Union Lux. Due to his interest in quantum mechanics, he desires to explore the computational power, potential, and novelty of quantum computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maria Canon</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/maria-canon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/maria-canon/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Psychology, Class of 2022 I am a physics major who has always been fascinating by the quantum world and I would love to see where this club would be able to take me. I have taken basic quantum mechanics just this semester as well as Science of complex systems and have completed all the prereqs for the Physics BS major.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Tu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/matt-tu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/matt-tu/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github Through my CS major, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot about the inner workings about bit-centered traditional computing, including its physical limitations. I&amp;rsquo;m really interested in potentially being one of the first people to &amp;ldquo;write code&amp;rdquo; for that runs on a quantum computer. I feel like my background in lower-level systems programming can be a huge asset for the organization, and as a non-Physics major I can learn a lot about quantum mechanics in general!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Li</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/richard-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/richard-li/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Economics, Class of 2022 Github Richard Li is a junior in Pauli Murray College studying Physics and Economics. He is interested in learning more about how exactly a robust quantum computer is built, as well as the ingenious algorithms that allow it to solve amazingly challenging problems. In his free time, he enjoys playing soccer, watching Youtube videos, and learning the guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sami Alves</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sami-alves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sami-alves/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebastian Tsai</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sebastian-tsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sebastian-tsai/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaun Radgowski</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shaun-radgowski/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shaun-radgowski/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2021 Github I am currently doing my senior thesis in the Physics major on Variational Hybrid Algorithms for Quantum Computers. This research comprises designing an alternative to the QAOA optimizer with a different underlying cost function. I have also competed in an IBM Qiskit hackathon, and I have really enjoyed learning about quantum computing and learning to use the various programming libraries. I am interested in being more involved in the QC community to learn from others and help new interested students learn more about the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Devulapalli</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sri-devulapalli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sri-devulapalli/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Sri, a freshman in Berkeley College studying physics. My interests are broadly in quantum algorithms and cosmology. I have some previous research experience with radio telescopes. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to chat about anything related to astronomy, finance, poker, or Texas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sukhman Singh</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sukhman-singh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sukhman-singh/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2021 Sukhman is a senior in Saybrook majoring in Mathematics and Physics. Excited about pursuing higher studies in physics, he likes to take advantage of any opportunity that sheds light on all things quantum. He hopes to learn more about the current state of quantum computing and is looking forward to advancing this club&amp;rsquo;s goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yiğit Kılıçoğlu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yigit-kilicoglu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yigit-kilicoglu/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Physics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn Yiğit is interested in the mathematics of quantum computation. Having a background in programming, he is also into quantum cryptography. Outside of academics, Yiğit is an avid tennis, piano and accordion player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yofti Milkessa</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yofti-milkessa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yofti-milkessa/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn I’m a CS major who has also dabbled in physics. I was curious about the idea of quantum computing so after a friend’s recommendation, I read Nielsen and Chuang’s book on quantum computation during the summer. I have since been even more fascinated about this field and I want to keep exploring it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yu Jun Shen</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yu-jun-shen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yu-jun-shen/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github Quantum computing is a rapidly developing field and can help us solve big problems in the near future. I want to learn more about this and Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing group is a great way to further my interest. I hope to meet fellow Yalies who are excited about this and explore some spooky physics soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Classes towards Quantum Information Science</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/yale-classes-towards-quantum-information-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/yale-classes-towards-quantum-information-science/</guid>
      <description>Here is a growing list of Yale classes with applications towards Quantum Information Science. Much more coming soon.
Quantum Information  Physics 345: Introduction to Quantum Information Processing and Communication, Prof Steven Girvin  Who should take it: Anyone with a knowledge of complex numbers and introductory linear algebra. This course presents a very accessible and exciting foray into quantum information science. This is highly recommended to anyone looking to begin their journey with quantum computing, with or without a technical physics background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yale Quantum Institute</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/yale-quantum-institute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/yale-quantum-institute/</guid>
      <description>Here is a growing list of interdisciplinary Yale efforts in Quantum Computing under the umbrella of the Yale Quantum Institute.
Useful Sites  quantuminstitute.yale.edu  Yale Quantum Institute Events Institute History Institute Members Join the mailing list!   quantum.yale.edu  A collection of quantum computing research efforts and labs at Yale looking into topics spanning Physics, Applied Physics, Chemistry, Computer Science, and Engineering. Information about the Quantum Week at Yale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open-source Resources</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/open-source-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/open-source-resources/</guid>
      <description>Here are some resources to help you along with your open source quantum endeavours.
QC Open Source Projects
Quantum Open Source Foundation
 Open Source Projects Mentorship Learning Prizes and Funding Projects  Unitary Fund
 Non-profit Microgrants Research projects  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit/</guid>
      <description>Qiskit is IBM&amp;rsquo;s open source quantum computing SDK. There is a vibrant community of open source developers and quantum advocates.
Getting Started Join the Qiskit slack!
Here are some curated tutorials to get yourself started with Qiskit and the IBM Quantum Experience:
 Code your first quantum circuit CH 1-3 of Qiskit Textbook Beginner Tutorials  Events Stay up to date with Qiskit events.
Past events:
 Hackathons IBM Qiskit Global Summer School  Quantum Advocates Apply to become one of ~200 Quantum Advocate across ~30 countries at IBM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit Surface Code Encoder and MWPM Decoder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</guid>
      <description>Please check out this Surface Code Encoder and Minimum Weight Perfect Matching Decoder created by members Shantanu Jha &amp;lsquo;21, Henry Liu &amp;lsquo;21 and Will Sun &amp;lsquo;22 for IBM Qiskit Ignis.
Here is the Github repo: https://github.com/Phionx/qiskit_surface_codes
This open-source package was presented at the November 2020 Qiskit Advocate Demo Session and is pending official incorporating into Qiskit Ignis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qubit by Qubit Initiative</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qubit-by-qubit-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qubit-by-qubit-initiative/</guid>
      <description>Apply for paid and volunteer opportunities at the Qubit by Qubit Initiative.
Here are some of their current projects:
 Developing homework, problem sets, or worksheets Developing middle or high school curricula for quantum Developing or editing content for textbook for high school students Developing quantum workshop for K-12 students Being a Teaching Assistant for intro course Teaching quantum workshops to K-12 students  Please reach out to member Shoumik Chowdhury &amp;lsquo;21 to learn more!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
