<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/categories/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Cryptography</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-cryptography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-cryptography/</guid>
      <description>About We are going through an edX course titled &amp;ldquo;Quantum Cryptography&amp;rdquo; to gain knowledge and experience in the field. Once a sufficient amount of fundamental concepts is learned, we will start to implement quantum network protocols for the Quantum Protocol Zoo, an open repository founded by our very own Shraddha Singh.
Project Lead: Argyris Giannisis Manes,
Yiğit Kılıçoğlu.
Team: Sami Alves,
Ryan Bose-Roy,
Ines Chung-Halpern,
Sofia Fausone,
Francis Fedora,
Argyris Giannisis Manes,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Error Correction Study Group</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-error-correction-study-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-error-correction-study-group/</guid>
      <description>About This project was started during the Spring semester of 2021, and the original project proposal can be found here. During this semester, a team of two members created a presentation on a topic related to quantum error correction each week. Going into the summmer, we will switch to a reading group format. Each week we wil have a reading addressing an aspect of quantum error correction. With the help of our graduate student mentor Alec, we will break down challenging topics, with the goal of gaining familiarity with the language and concepts of the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Programming API</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-programming-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-programming-api/</guid>
      <description>About The goal of this project is to provide a quantum programming API that will help people who want to incorporate quantum speed-ups into their classical programs much easier.
This project aims to both create the infrastructure to communicate with quantum systems and to create with that same infrastructure. We hope that our efforts in building this can lead to inspiration and further advances with the use of quantum computing in the broader computer science community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Coalition Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-coalition-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-coalition-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Attend Please visit quantumcoalition.io to learn more about this exciting virtual hackathon co-hosted by Yale and Stanford, open to everyone, and sponsored by Quantum Computing industry innovators.
Registration launches on February 14, 2021!
Join the Organizing Committee If you are a YuQC member interested in joining the QC Hack Organizing Committee, please sign up here.
Sponsors Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Ideas</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/project-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/project-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Projects: efforts ranging open-source packages to hackathon events to resource development and more!
SUBMIT YOUR PROJECT IDEAS: Have an idea for a project? Click here to propose a project!
NOTE: Each project requires a corresponding project proposal that can be filled out and submitted later. Click here for the template for the write-up.
Join a project team: Want to see what we&amp;rsquo;re working on? Click here to check out our project spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit Surface Code Encoder and MWPM Decoder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</guid>
      <description>Status This open-source package was presented at the November 2020 Qiskit Advocate Demo Session and is pending official incorporating into Qiskit Ignis. Our ultimate goal is to create general Topological Code interfaces, with sepecific implementations using the CSS (XXXX/ZZZZ) surface code, XZZX surface code, and repetition code,
 About We are building Encoder and Minimum Weight Perfect Matching Graph Decoder tools for serveral Topological Codes we wish to implement in Qiskit Ignis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qubit by Qubit Initiative</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qubit-by-qubit-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qubit-by-qubit-initiative/</guid>
      <description>Apply for paid and volunteer opportunities at the Qubit by Qubit Initiative.
Here are some of their current projects:
 Developing homework, problem sets, or worksheets Developing middle or high school curricula for quantum Developing or editing content for textbook for high school students Developing quantum workshop for K-12 students Being a Teaching Assistant for intro course Teaching quantum workshops to K-12 students  Please reach out to member Shoumik Chowdhury &amp;lsquo;21 to learn more!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
