<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/categories/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.github.io/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Ideas</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/project-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/project-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Please enter your project ideas here: forms.gle/93Nfbqi15hT6x1bM7
Join our discord to discuss ideas with members. Please email yaleqc@yale.edu to get an invite link!
Much more coming soon&amp;hellip;
Event Ideas  Yale QC Hackathon  Yale Quantum Institute Sponsorship IBM Sponsorship Partnership with Stanford    Open Source Project Ideas  Surface Code Encoder and MWPM Decoder  Talk Ideas Tutorial Ideas Resource Ideas </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit Surface Code Encoder and MWPM Decoder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</guid>
      <description>Please check out this Surface Code Encoder and Minimum Weight Perfect Matching Decoder created by members Shantanu Jha &amp;lsquo;21, Henry Liu &amp;lsquo;21 and Will Sun &amp;lsquo;22 for IBM Qiskit Ignis.
Here is the Github repo: https://github.com/Phionx/qiskit_surface_codes
This open-source package was presented at the November 2020 Qiskit Advocate Demo Session and is pending official incorporating into Qiskit Ignis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qubit by Qubit Initiative</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qubit-by-qubit-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qubit-by-qubit-initiative/</guid>
      <description>Apply for paid and volunteer opportunities at the Qubit by Qubit Initiative.
Here are some of their current projects:
 Developing homework, problem sets, or worksheets Developing middle or high school curricula for quantum Developing or editing content for textbook for high school students Developing quantum workshop for K-12 students Being a Teaching Assistant for intro course Teaching quantum workshops to K-12 students  Please reach out to member Shoumik Chowdhury &amp;lsquo;21 to learn more!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
