<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Members on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/categories/members/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Members on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.github.io/categories/members/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andy Ding (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/andy-ding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/andy-ding/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Ph.D. Student LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayelet Kalfus (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ayelet-kalfus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ayelet-kalfus/</guid>
      <description>Physics with Computer Science certificate, Class of 2024 (Gap Year) LinkedIn, Github Ayelet Kalfus is a rising sophomore majoring in physics, with a certificate in computer science. Intrigued by quantum computers’ potential to transform our lives, Ayelet is super excited to join YuQC, learning with and from the entire group. Outside of physics, Ayelet loves reading, writing, film, and exploring new cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang/</guid>
      <description>Math and Humanities, Class of 2024 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikhil Harle (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/nikhil-harle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/nikhil-harle/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 Github Nikhil is a rising junior and intensive physics major and was previously a fellow at the Center for Quantum Devices in Copenhagen. His interests include preserving quantum information through novel methods of error correction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seun Omonije (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/seun-omonije/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/seun-omonije/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github Quantum computing is so interesting to me because it&amp;rsquo;s uncharted territory. There is so much to be built and so much to be learned in this field, and I want to be at the forefront of this new era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shantanu Jha (President 2020-21, Founder)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shantanu-jha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shantanu-jha/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Mathematics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github, Email Shantanu ’21 is a Math and Physics major and a member of Saybrook College. He founded YuQC to provide a support network to help younger or otherwise newcomer students explore the often daunting but wonderfully interdisciplinary field of quantum information science. His research spans quantum information theory work with Steven Girvin, terahertz wireless communications (6G) with Federico Capasso, and most recently, experimental quantum computation with Michel Devoret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoumik Chowdhury (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github As a long-time enthusiast of quantum computing, I am so excited that a club like YuQC now exists at Yale. I am really looking forward to meeting other people interested in quantum, and getting to learn from them — as well as being able to share what I have learned during my years working in this area. Given that Yale is a world-leading institution for quantum information science, it is only fitting that we have a proper undergraduate club dedicated to this field — I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what this club gets up to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Householder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/aaron-householder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/aaron-householder/</guid>
      <description>Astrophysics, Class of 2023 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aidan Evans</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/aidan-evans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/aidan-evans/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Philosophy, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allen Mi</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/allen-mi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/allen-mi/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Computer Science, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Foxman</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ben-foxman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ben-foxman/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Computer Science, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github I&amp;rsquo;m a sophomore in Pauli Murray College, double majoring in computer science and math. Quantum Computation interests me because of how many applications would be unlocked when the physical limitations of classical computers. I&amp;rsquo;m especially curious about the vast improvements that could be made to artificial intelligence, and what would be possible for Quantum Computers to &amp;ldquo;learn&amp;rdquo; in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Yee</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/brandon-yee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/brandon-yee/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2024 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam Greene</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/cam-greene/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/cam-greene/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Philosophy, Class of 2024 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connor Totilas</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/connor-totilas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/connor-totilas/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2024 I remember learning in 9th grade what a qubit was and I though it was the coolest thing ever. I find quantum mechanics to be absolutely fascinating and to me quantum information science is the pinnacle of our ability to harness quantum mechanics. I soon began teaching myself all about quantum computers until I was able to write a research paper about the fundamental properties of quantum computers my senior year in high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Qenani</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/daniel-qenani/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/daniel-qenani/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 LinkedIn I would like to be a part of this club in whatever capacity is most useful for the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanbai Lyu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/hanbai-lyu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/hanbai-lyu/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Mathematics, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hao Chen</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/hao-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/hao-chen/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Visiting Student 2019-2020 LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry Liu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/henry-liu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/henry-liu/</guid>
      <description>Applied Physics, Class of 2021 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang-huaijin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang-huaijin/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Philosophy, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessie Chen</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jessie-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jessie-chen/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Computer Science, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel Binu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/joel-binu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/joel-binu/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Blanco</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jorge-blanco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jorge-blanco/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and either Statistics and Data Science or Computer Science, Class of 2023-4 (Gap Semester) LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katerina Kargioti</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/katerina-kargioti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/katerina-kargioti/</guid>
      <description>Applied Physics, Class of 2023 Hi! My name is Katerina and I am a sophomore in Pauli Murray College. I am majoring in Applied Physis. I am interested in learning more about quantum computation due its potential to open new pathways for physics and science in general. It is also exciting to be part of a fast-growing field that is constantly developing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keon Azar</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/keon-azar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/keon-azar/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Economics, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kohsuke Sato</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/kohsuke-sato/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/kohsuke-sato/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github I am a junior majoring in Physics (Int.), and quantum computing is an area that I would like to pursue after graduation. This club interested me because I thought that this would be a great opportunity for myself to learn more about quantum computing and to get to know other students interested in it at Yale!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lenny Khazan</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/lenny-khazan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/lenny-khazan/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2021 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke Bell</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/luke-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/luke-bell/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics, Class of 2023 LinkedIn Luke Bell is a sophomore in Pierson College and a current mathematics major. On campus, he is involved in the Yale Federalist Party, Yale Undergraduate Piano Collective, Rural Students Alliance at Yale, the Yale Logos Magazine, and Christian Union Lux. Due to his interest in quantum mechanics, he desires to explore the computational power, potential, and novelty of quantum computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maria Canon</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/maria-canon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/maria-canon/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Psychology, Class of 2022 I am a physics major who has always been fascinating by the quantum world and I would love to see where this club would be able to take me. I have taken basic quantum mechanics just this semester as well as Science of complex systems and have completed all the prereqs for the Physics BS major.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Tu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/matt-tu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/matt-tu/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github Through my CS major, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot about the inner workings about bit-centered traditional computing, including its physical limitations. I&amp;rsquo;m really interested in potentially being one of the first people to &amp;ldquo;write code&amp;rdquo; for that runs on a quantum computer. I feel like my background in lower-level systems programming can be a huge asset for the organization, and as a non-Physics major I can learn a lot about quantum mechanics in general!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Li</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/richard-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/richard-li/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Economics, Class of 2022 Github Richard Li is a junior in Pauli Murray College studying Physics and Economics. He is interested in learning more about how exactly a robust quantum computer is built, as well as the ingenious algorithms that allow it to solve amazingly challenging problems. In his free time, he enjoys playing soccer, watching Youtube videos, and learning the guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sami Alves</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sami-alves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sami-alves/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebastian Tsai</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sebastian-tsai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sebastian-tsai/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaun Radgowski</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shaun-radgowski/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shaun-radgowski/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2021 Github I am currently doing my senior thesis in the Physics major on Variational Hybrid Algorithms for Quantum Computers. This research comprises designing an alternative to the QAOA optimizer with a different underlying cost function. I have also competed in an IBM Qiskit hackathon, and I have really enjoyed learning about quantum computing and learning to use the various programming libraries. I am interested in being more involved in the QC community to learn from others and help new interested students learn more about the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Devulapalli</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sri-devulapalli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sri-devulapalli/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Sri, a freshman in Berkeley College studying physics. My interests are broadly in quantum algorithms and cosmology. I have some previous research experience with radio telescopes. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to chat about anything related to astronomy, finance, poker, or Texas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sukhman Singh</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sukhman-singh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/sukhman-singh/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2021 Sukhman is a senior in Saybrook majoring in Mathematics and Physics. Excited about pursuing higher studies in physics, he likes to take advantage of any opportunity that sheds light on all things quantum. He hopes to learn more about the current state of quantum computing and is looking forward to advancing this club&amp;rsquo;s goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yiğit Kılıçoğlu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yigit-kilicoglu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yigit-kilicoglu/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Physics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn Yiğit is interested in the mathematics of quantum computation. Having a background in programming, he is also into quantum cryptography. Outside of academics, Yiğit is an avid tennis, piano and accordion player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yofti Milkessa</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yofti-milkessa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yofti-milkessa/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn I’m a CS major who has also dabbled in physics. I was curious about the idea of quantum computing so after a friend’s recommendation, I read Nielsen and Chuang’s book on quantum computation during the summer. I have since been even more fascinated about this field and I want to keep exploring it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yu Jun Shen</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yu-jun-shen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/yu-jun-shen/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github Quantum computing is a rapidly developing field and can help us solve big problems in the near future. I want to learn more about this and Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing group is a great way to further my interest. I hope to meet fellow Yalies who are excited about this and explore some spooky physics soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
