<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Members on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/categories/members/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Members on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/categories/members/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andy Ding (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/andy-ding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/andy-ding/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Ph.D. Student LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayelet Kalfus (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/ayelet-kalfus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/ayelet-kalfus/</guid>
      <description>Director of Partnerships (2020-21) Physics with Computer Science certificate, Class of 2024 (Gap Year) LinkedIn, Github Ayelet Kalfus is a rising sophomore majoring in physics, with a certificate in computer science. Intrigued by quantum computers’ potential to transform our lives, Ayelet is super excited to join YuQC, learning with and from the entire group. Outside of physics, Ayelet loves reading, writing, film, and exploring new cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/jean-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/jean-wang/</guid>
      <description>Director of Invited Talks (2020-21) Math and Humanities, Class of 2024 Github Jean is a first-year in Jonathan Edwards College planning to double major in Mathematics and Humanities. She is interested in the mathematics of quantum cryptography and optimizing quantum algorithms. Outside of quantum, she enjoys writing stories and listening to radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessie Chen (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/jessie-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/jessie-chen/</guid>
      <description>Treasurer Physics and Computer Science, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikhil Harle (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/nikhil-harle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/nikhil-harle/</guid>
      <description>Director of Events Physics, Class of 2023 Github Nikhil is a rising junior and intensive physics major and was previously a fellow at the Center for Quantum Devices in Copenhagen. His interests include preserving quantum information through novel methods of error correction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sami Alves (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/sami-alves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/sami-alves/</guid>
      <description>Social Chair Physics and Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seun Omonije (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/seun-omonije/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/seun-omonije/</guid>
      <description>Director of Open Source Projects (2020-21) Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn | Github Bio: Oluseun (Seun) Omonije &amp;lsquo;22 is a Computer Science major from Dallas, TX in Silliman College. A two-time Google Intern, Seun got started in quantum during the summer of 2020 while attending a Google AI Quantum event. Since then, he spent a semester as a research assistant for Prof. Lin Zhong&amp;rsquo;s Efficient Computing Lab, helping to solve problems pertaining to quantum error correction, specifically optimizations to the control system between QEC decoders and physical quantum system, as well as the algorithms running within these control systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoumik Chowdhury (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</guid>
      <description>Director of Resources (2020-21) Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github As a long-time enthusiast of quantum computing, I am incredibly excited that a club like YuQC now exists at Yale. I am really looking forward to meeting other people interested in quantum science, and getting to learn from them — as well as being able to share what I have learned during my years working in this area. Given that Yale is a world-leading institution for quantum information science, it is only fitting that we have a proper undergraduate club dedicated to this field — I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what this group gets up to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben McDonough (Project Leader 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/ben-mcdonough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/ben-mcdonough/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2024 Github Ben is a sophomore in the class of 2024. Ben is a physics major but loves math and computer science as well, and he feels drawn to the interdisciplinary nature of the quantum community. He believes that studying quantum information is a method for investigating fundamental properties of nature. He conducted research under Professor Girvin during the summer of ‘21 into quantum error correction, and he would love to talk to you about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Argyrios Giannisis Manes (Project Leader 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/argyrios-giannisis-manes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/argyrios-giannisis-manes/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn, Github Argyris Giannisis Manes is a first-year in Trumbull College, was born in Athens and now lives in Volos, Greece. He intends to major in Mathematics and Physics, and his interests include Math, Physics, CS, Astronomy, Music, Debate, Juggling, and more! He’s been interested in Quantum Computing for a long time, and is really excited to finally have the opportunity to explore Quantum Information alongside peers and mentors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Foxman (Project Leader 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/ben-foxman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/ben-foxman/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Computer Science, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github I&amp;rsquo;m a sophomore in Pauli Murray College, double majoring in computer science and math. Quantum Computation interests me because of how many applications would be unlocked when the physical limitations of classical computers. I&amp;rsquo;m especially curious about the vast improvements that could be made to artificial intelligence, and what would be possible for Quantum Computers to &amp;ldquo;learn&amp;rdquo; in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yiğit Kılıçoğlu (Project Leader 20-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/yigit-kilicoglu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/yigit-kilicoglu/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Physics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn Yiğit is interested in the mathematics of quantum computation. Having a background in programming, he is also into quantum cryptography. Outside of academics, Yiğit is an avid tennis, piano and accordion player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Householder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/aaron-householder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/aaron-householder/</guid>
      <description>Astrophysics, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barkotel Fesseha Zemenu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/barkotel-zemenu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/barkotel-zemenu/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2024 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deyuan Li</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/deyuan-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/deyuan-li/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Mathematics, Class of 2024 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Francis Fedora</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/francis-fedora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/francis-fedora/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2023 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aidan Evans</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/aidan-evans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/aidan-evans/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science and Philosophy, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github Aidan Evans is a sophomore double majoring and computer science and philosophy. He has completed courses in advanced algorithm design and theory of computation for traditional computers along with extensive programming experience in multiple languages. He hopes to learn more about quantum computation and gain experience designing and programming quantum algorithms. In general, Aidan enjoys to challenge himself and apply what he has learned in practical and meaningful ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allen Mi</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/allen-mi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/allen-mi/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Computer Science, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amanda Butler</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/amanda-butler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/amanda-butler/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Astronomy, Class of 2022 Amanda (JE &amp;lsquo;22) is a double major in Physics &amp;amp; Astronomy, broadly interested in experimental techniques and cosmology. She is eager to explore Quantum Computing &amp;amp; Information Science since she has had less exposure to it in her primary fields, but is excited for the ways in which QC will likely revolutionize all scientific disciplines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Yee</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/brandon-yee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/brandon-yee/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2024 Github I got pulled over for speeding once. The officer asked me if I knew how fast I was going. I said &amp;ldquo;no, but I know where I am.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry Liu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/henry-liu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/henry-liu/</guid>
      <description>Applied Physics, Class of 2021 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang Huaijin</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/jean-wang-huaijin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/jean-wang-huaijin/</guid>
      <description>Physics and Philosophy, Class of 2022 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Blanco</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/jorge-blanco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/jorge-blanco/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics and Statistics and Data Science, Class of 2023-4 (Gap Semester) LinkedIn, Github Jorge Blanco is a sophomore studying Mathematics and Statistics and Data Science. His academic interests are quantitative finance and mathematical statistics. He is interested in learning about quantum computation because its applications have world-changing potential. Specifically, he is interested in exploring the ways quantum computation, through the use of quantum optimization algorithms, can be applied to solve problems in finance and other fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katerina Kargioti</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/katerina-kargioti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/katerina-kargioti/</guid>
      <description>Applied Physics, Class of 2023 Github Hi! My name is Katerina and I am a sophomore in Pauli Murray College. I am majoring in Applied Physis. I am interested in learning more about quantum computation due its potential to open new pathways for physics and science in general. It is also exciting to be part of a fast-growing field that is constantly developing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luke Bell</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/luke-bell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/luke-bell/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics, Class of 2023 LinkedIn Luke Bell is a sophomore in Pierson College and a current mathematics major. On campus, he is involved in the Yale Federalist Party, Yale Undergraduate Piano Collective, Rural Students Alliance at Yale, the Yale Logos Magazine, and Christian Union Lux. Due to his interest in quantum mechanics, he desires to explore the computational power, potential, and novelty of quantum computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matt Tu</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/matt-tu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/matt-tu/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github Through my CS major, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot about the inner workings about bit-centered traditional computing, including its physical limitations. I&amp;rsquo;m really interested in potentially being one of the first people to &amp;ldquo;write code&amp;rdquo; for that runs on a quantum computer. I feel like my background in lower-level systems programming can be a huge asset for the organization, and as a non-Physics major I can learn a lot about quantum mechanics in general!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sofia Fausone</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/sofia-fausone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/sofia-fausone/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Mathematics, Class of 2024 LinkedIn, Github Sofia is interested in learning more about quantum mechanics and quantum computing in particular. In high school, she participated in a summer research program about quantum mechanics and nanotechnology, focusing on coding and STMs. She is excited to explore quantum computation, especially since it is a fairly new field with enormous potential for physics and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yofti Milkessa</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/yofti-milkessa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/yofti-milkessa/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn I’m a CS major who has also dabbled in physics. I was curious about the idea of quantum computing so after a friend’s recommendation, I read Nielsen and Chuang’s book on quantum computation during the summer. I have since been even more fascinated about this field and I want to keep exploring it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yu Jun Shen</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/yu-jun-shen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/yu-jun-shen/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering, Class of 2023 LinkedIn, Github Quantum computing is a rapidly developing field and can help us solve big problems in the near future. I want to learn more about this and Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing group is a great way to further my interest. I hope to meet fellow Yalies who are excited about this and explore some spooky physics soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laura Zhou</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/laura-zhou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/laura-zhou/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Class of 2022 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ines Chung-Halpern</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/ines-chung-halpern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/ines-chung-halpern/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malcolm Keyes</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/malcolm-keyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/malcolm-keyes/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science, Class of 2023 Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suba Ramesh</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/suba-ramesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/suba-ramesh/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Class of 2024 LinkedIn, Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Doyle</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/members/will-doyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/members/will-doyle/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Engineering, Class of 2022 LinkedIn, Github Will took physics 260-261 with Professor Girvin and thought that quantum computing sounds really interesting!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
