<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>open-source on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/tags/open-source/</link>
    <description>Recent content in open-source on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.github.io/tags/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Ideas</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/project-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/project-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Projects: efforts ranging open-source packages to hackathon events to resource development and more!
SUBMIT YOUR PROJECT IDEAS: Have an idea for a project? Click here to propose a project!
NOTE: Each project requires a corresponding project proposal that can be filled out and submitted later. Click here for the template for the write-up.
Get involved with a current project: Want to see what we&amp;rsquo;re working on? Click here to check out our project spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open-source Resources</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/open-source-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/open-source-resources/</guid>
      <description>Here are some resources to help you along with your open source quantum endeavours.
QC Open Source Projects
Quantum Open Source Foundation
 Open Source Projects Mentorship Learning Prizes and Funding Projects  Unitary Fund
 Non-profit Microgrants Research projects  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit/</guid>
      <description>Qiskit is IBM&amp;rsquo;s open source quantum computing SDK. There is a vibrant community of open source developers and quantum advocates.
Getting Started Join the Qiskit slack!
Here are some curated tutorials to get yourself started with Qiskit and the IBM Quantum Experience:
 Code your first quantum circuit CH 1-3 of Qiskit Textbook Beginner Tutorials  Events Stay up to date with Qiskit events.
Past events:
 Hackathons IBM Qiskit Global Summer School  Quantum Advocates Apply to become one of ~200 Quantum Advocate across ~30 countries at IBM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit Surface Code Encoder and MWPM Decoder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</guid>
      <description>About We are building a Surface Code Encoder and Minimum Weight Perfect Matching Decoder package for Qiskit Ignis.
Here is the Github repo: https://github.com/Phionx/qiskit_surface_codes
Here is a link to our project proposal.
Status This open-source package was presented at the November 2020 Qiskit Advocate Demo Session and is pending official incorporating into Qiskit Ignis. Our immediate goal is to demonstrate the rotated surface code threshold point in simulation.
Team The first iteration of this project was created by members Shantanu Jha &amp;lsquo;21, Henry Liu &amp;lsquo;21 and Will Sun &amp;lsquo;22 for IBM Qiskit Ignis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
