<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>quantum error correction on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/tags/quantum-error-correction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in quantum error correction on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/tags/quantum-error-correction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Error Correction Study Group</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-error-correction-study-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-error-correction-study-group/</guid>
      <description>About We concluded the study group with our last meeting on 8/17/2021! We are looking forward to the next academic year, and look for a future iteration at the next YuQC meeting!
This is a study group that was started during the spring semester of 2021, and met weekly through August of the following summer. We would like to thank our graduate mentor Alec Eikbusch for his tremendous support of this group, fielding our questions in-person and over discord, and setting up meetings with postdocs and other graduate students who are actively working in this field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>qtcodes</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qtcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qtcodes/</guid>
      <description>Status qtcodes is published on PyPI with tooling to encode, decode and benchmark XXXX/ZZZZ surface code, XZZX surface code, and repetition code!
About We are building Encoder and Minimum Weight Perfect Matching Graph Decoder tools for serveral Topological Codes we wish to implement in Qiskit Ignis.
Here is the Github repo: https://github.com/yaleqc/qtcodes
Here is a link to our project proposal.
Team The first iteration of this project was created by members Shantanu Jha &amp;lsquo;21, Henry Liu &amp;lsquo;21, Will Sun &amp;lsquo;22, Shraddha Singh (Grad), and Andy Ding (Grad).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
