<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>quantum error correction on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.com/tags/quantum-error-correction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in quantum error correction on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.com/tags/quantum-error-correction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Error Correction Study Group</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-error-correction-study-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/quantum-error-correction-study-group/</guid>
      <description>About We are exploring quantum error correction. We will start with the quantum repition code, and move into more complicated examples of quantum error correction. Every week, one project member will prepare a short presentation addressing that week&amp;rsquo;s topic. Each topic will be accompanied by a short weekly project, which will be a textbook problem, a qiskit exercise, or a challenge based on the last week’s presentation. A full introduction and background on this project can be found on our project proposal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit Surface Code Encoder and MWPM Decoder</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.com/p/qiskit-surface-code-encoder-and-mwpm-decoder/</guid>
      <description>Status This open-source package was presented at the November 2020 Qiskit Advocate Demo Session and is pending official incorporating into Qiskit Ignis. Our ultimate goal is to create general Topological Code interfaces, with sepecific implementations using the CSS (XXXX/ZZZZ) surface code, XZZX surface code, and repetition code,
 About We are building Encoder and Minimum Weight Perfect Matching Graph Decoder tools for serveral Topological Codes we wish to implement in Qiskit Ignis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
