<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>board on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</title>
    <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/tags/board/</link>
    <description>Recent content in board on Yale Undergraduate Quantum Computing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yaleqc.github.io/tags/board/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Andy Ding (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/andy-ding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/andy-ding/</guid>
      <description>Physics, Ph.D. Student LinkedIn </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ayelet Kalfus (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ayelet-kalfus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/ayelet-kalfus/</guid>
      <description>Director of Partnerships (2020-21) Physics with Computer Science certificate, Class of 2024 (Gap Year) LinkedIn Ayelet Kalfus is a rising sophomore majoring in physics, with a certificate in computer science. Intrigued by quantum computers’ potential to transform our lives, Ayelet is super excited to join YuQC, learning with and from the entire group. Outside of physics, Ayelet loves reading, writing, film, and exploring new cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean Wang (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/jean-wang/</guid>
      <description>Director of Invited Talks (2020-21) Math and Humanities, Class of 2024 Github Jean is a first-year in Jonathan Edwards College planning to double major in Mathematics and Humanities. She is interested in the mathematics of quantum cryptography and optimizing quantum algorithms. Outside of quantum, she enjoys writing stories and listening to radio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikhil Harle (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/nikhil-harle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/nikhil-harle/</guid>
      <description>Director of Events Physics, Class of 2023 Github Nikhil is a rising junior and intensive physics major and was previously a fellow at the Center for Quantum Devices in Copenhagen. His interests include preserving quantum information through novel methods of error correction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seun Omonije (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/seun-omonije/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/seun-omonije/</guid>
      <description>Director of Open Source Projects (2020-21) Computer Science, Class of 2022 LinkedIn | Github Bio: Oluseun (Seun) Omonije &amp;lsquo;22 is a Computer Science major from Dallas, TX in Silliman College. A two-time Google Intern, Seun got started in quantum during the summer of 2020 while attending a Google AI Quantum event. Since then, he spent a semester as a research assistant for Prof. Lin Zhong&amp;rsquo;s Efficient Computing Lab, helping to solve problems pertaining to quantum error correction, specifically optimizations to the control system between QEC decoders and physical quantum system, as well as the algorithms running within these control systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shantanu Jha (President 2020-21, Founder)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shantanu-jha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shantanu-jha/</guid>
      <description>President (2020-21) Physics and Mathematics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github, Email Shantanu ’21 is a Math and Physics major and a member of Saybrook College. He founded YuQC to provide a support network to help younger or otherwise newcomer students explore the often daunting but wonderfully interdisciplinary field of quantum information science. His research spans quantum information theory work with Steven Girvin, terahertz wireless communications (6G) with Federico Capasso, and most recently, experimental quantum computation with Michel Devoret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoumik Chowdhury (Board 2020-21)</title>
      <link>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yaleqc.github.io/members/shoumik-chowdhury/</guid>
      <description>Director of Resources (2020-21) Mathematics and Physics, Class of 2021 LinkedIn, Github As a long-time enthusiast of quantum computing, I am incredibly excited that a club like YuQC now exists at Yale. I am really looking forward to meeting other people interested in quantum science, and getting to learn from them — as well as being able to share what I have learned during my years working in this area. Given that Yale is a world-leading institution for quantum information science, it is only fitting that we have a proper undergraduate club dedicated to this field — I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what this group gets up to!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
